https://www.suffolkfcu.org/privacy-policy

closeAttention Members: Visit our Covid-19 Information Page for updated information on Branch Operations, Ways to Bank from Home, Member Assistance and Personal Protective Measures.Close
[Skip to Content]Branch Appointment FormPersonalCheckingCheckingFree Advantage CheckingMax Money CheckingGirl Scouts CheckingSharks CheckingCourtesy PayMasterCard® Debit CardDirect DepositSavingsPersonal SavingsShare SavingsMoney Market SavingsShare CertificatesIRAsSavings Club AccountsYouth Savings AccountsLoans & MortgagesLoans & MortgagesMortgagesHome Equity Loans and Lines-of-CreditPersonal Loans and Lines-of-CreditAuto and Boat LoansCredit CardsLoan InsuranceCalculatorsPersonal Banking RatesFee ScheduleInvestments & InsuranceInvestments & InsuranceFinancial PlanningInsuranceRetirement & InvestmentsFinancial CounselingFinancial Literacy WorkshopsMortgagesBusinessBusiness LoansBusiness LoansMasterCard® Business Rewards Credit CardCommercial LoansBusiness SavingsBusiness Banking RatesFee ScheduleCommercial LendingCheckingCorporate PartnersMerchant ServicesPayroll ServicesOnline Servicese-StatementsMobile BankingRemote Check DepositDigital WalletCardValetCard LockOnline Banking & Bill PayWire TransfersOpen or ApplyApply for a LoanOpen an AccountAbout UsCOVID-19 InformationAbout Suffolk FederalATM LocationsBenefits of MembershipBlog, News & EventsBranch LocationsContact UsCareerseMagazineFormsNotices & DisclosuresSecurity CenterCash App FraudHoliday ScamsCredit & Debit Card MonitoringHelpful ResourcesIdentity TheftScams You Need to KnowCyber SafetySuffolk County Community College PartnershipSuffolk County Community College PartnershipScholarship ProgramSharks CheckingStudent Resource CenterPrivacy PolicySuffolk Federal is committed to providing you with financial products and services to meet your financial needs. This Privacy Notice describes our policies and practices to protect your privacy and enable us to share information so we may provide our members competitive financial products and services.What follows is a description of the information we collect and disclose, including the parties who receive non-public information from us as we conduct credit union business.Information is collected about you from the following sources:Applications, forms and other information that you provide us, whether in writing, electronically, via the Internet, or by any other means. For information we collect about you when you visit or make transactions on our website, and for information about our use of “cookies” and online tracking technologies, please see our “Digital Privacy Practices”.Transactions on your shares and loansConsumer Reporting AgenciesVerification of information you provide on various formsParties to whom non-public personal information may be disclosed include:Financial service providers, such as those that provide mortgage, securities, credit card and insurance servicesNon-financial companies, such as consumer reporting agenciesDisclosure of information to parties that provide services to us:Suffolk Federal may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to the companies that perform marketing and other services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We may also disclose information about you under other circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of the credit union, follow your instructions as you authorize or protect the security of our financial records.Disclosure of information about former members:If you decide to terminate your membership or become an inactive member, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices as described in this notice.How we protect your information:We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your non-public personal information.What members can do to help:Protect your account numbers, PINs and passwordsBe cautious about disclosing your account number, social security number, etc., to other personsKeep your information with Suffolk Federal current so we can reach you if we detect potential problemsLet us know if you have questions. Don’t hesitate to call (631) 714-2974.Explanation of Opt Out Right:If you prefer that we do not disclose non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures, that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other then disclosures permitted by law). If you wish to opt out of disclosures to non-affiliated third parties, you may submit the following Opt Out Notice to any of our branches.Click here for a printed copy of our Privacy Policy and Opt Out NoticeIf you have any questions regarding our privacy policies or procedures, please contact us at (631) 714-2974.Digital Privacy PracticesSuffolk Federal is committed to safeguarding information about members and visitors to the Suffolk Federal website.The Suffolk Federal Privacy Notice explains our collection, use, retention and security of consumer information and applies to Suffolk Federal products and services offered for consumer (not business) purposes. Online activities of consumers may be subject to both the Suffolk Federal Privacy Policy and the Suffolk Federal Digital Privacy Practices.These Digital Privacy Practices explain our privacy practices regarding the information we collect about you when you visit or make transactions on Suffolk Federal’s website.How we may use information:We may collect information during your website visit in order to provide you with offers and information. We may also use the information we collect from you online to contact you via telephone, e-mail or other means regarding offers of products and services that may be of interest to you.How we collect information online:Cookies: Our web server may write a “cookie”, which is a small file, to your hard drive. We may use cookies to enhance your online experience, to facilitate your use of our website and to collect site-visitation statistics. If you are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, you can set your browser to refuse cookies.Tracer Technologies: Tracer, or spotlighting technologies may also be used by Suffolk Federal or its service providers. We may use tracers to determine whether you viewed certain advertisements or received or opened e-mails from Suffolk Federal.Information Storage:Suffolk Federal may store the information collected during your visit in an electronic database. Suffolk Federal uses security measures to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of data stored in our systems.Third Party Websites:This website may contain links to third-party sites that you may find useful. These sites have their own privacy policies. Links to other websites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Suffolk Federal website. We do not have any responsibility for, or control over, any of these sites, their content, or their privacy policies. You should review the privacy policy of any website before you provide any personal or confidential information. We do not endorse or make any representations about other websites, or any information, products, or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any third-party link, you do so entirely at your own risk.Privacy and Children:Suffolk Federal respects the privacy of children. We do not knowingly solicit data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children. We will not knowingly collect names or any other personally identifiable information from children. We recognize that protecting children’s identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and parents.Privacy PolicyDisclosuresThis credit union is federally insured by the National Credit Union Administration.
